It was the right thing. It was the wrong thing. It was
the only thing their hearts would allow.
The Sandpiper is a drama, romance film directed by Vincente Minnelli.
A free-spirited single mother forms a connection with the wedded headmaster
of an Episcopalian boarding school in Monterey, California.
Laura Reynolds, played by Elizabeth Taylor.
Edward Hewitt, played by Richard Burton.
Claire Hewitt, played by Eva Marie Saint.
Cos Erickson, played by Charles Bronson.
Ward Hendricks, played by Robert Webber.
Larry Brant, played by James Edwards.
The Sandpiper is a 1965 American drama film directed by Vincente Minnelli and starring Elizabeth
Taylor and Richard Burton, the third of eleven films starring the power couple.
The film explores the relationship between a repressed religious-school headmaster and a free-spirited
California artist in the years bridging the beatnik and hippie movements of the 60's.
The film explores themes of deer, love, school, unwed mother, big sur.
The tone is emotional.